Please subscribe to the Moyal Placement
Service channel to get free job updates.
Everyone is in demand for a
job in a bank. There have been a
lot of comments and messages saying that we
need a job in the bank line. So friends, today I have brought a
job in the bank line for you,
now that too with book hiring. Friends, what will be the
details? I will tell you all the details. That
too in ICICI Lombard, that is,
ICICI Bank, which is such a big brand,
we have vacancies. In any
vacancy that we have, we first talk
to the company and then bring it to you.
Along with this,
for your support, we have recruiters in Vasant, whom
you
can call and ask them to
connect with you for your interview and also
get information from them about what are the
selection chances and how can we apply for it.
Although I am going to tell all the details
in this video, but still, if
you need support,
you will find the number in the description box, but
before that, you must watch the video completely
and that is it.  Candidates should apply who
fulfill this criteria. So friends,
before I start today's video, those
who have not yet subscribed to the channel are
requested to subscribe to the channel,
like and share it.
We are getting a very good response from your side
and we are
trying to get all the candidates we have
placed as quickly as possible,
not in one company, but in 2 months. We have
companies in multiple locations, we are
trying them at various places to help them crack the interview
and at the same time we give
interview tips. So friends, let me start today's
video. The vacancy we have today is in
ICICI Lamp Board. First of all, let me
tell you that
in banking profiles, the jobs we have are of
Customer Relation Manager, Customer Relationship
Executive, Customer Relationship Officer,
what is their work going to be. Friends,
you must have seen that whenever you go to the bank,
a relationship executive comes to meet you,
he asks you what is the
problem or you go to their desk and
tell them that it is mostly from a private bank, not a
government bank, private bank.  We are talking about this
because in government banks, probably no
one asks you, no one
asks anyone, you can see the condition of SBI,
but here we are talking about a
reported ICICI Bank, so friends,
what happens there is that when you go to the desk, they
treat you very well, they
tell you what your problem is,
whatever your problem is, whatever
query you have, they solve it and
solve it face to face or you can
call them over the call,
you will see in your bank account, there is a
place where the
name and number of the relationship executive is kept, so you can call him and
take advice from him, he
helps you in every single thing, if
you want to take a loan or you want to take insurance, you want to
take something related to health or you
want to do FB etc. or anything like mutual
fund etc., they are your relationship
managers, they are relationship executives,
so you can call them, you
can meet them and get your queries
solved from them, so friends, overall
what I told you is this
There is going to be work for you people in ICICI,
now I will talk about
what the salary is going to be in it, friends, the
company provision is very good,
salary of 18000 to 32000 is available here, it
depends on experience, depend on
qualification and depend on your last
salary, I am saying it again, it is not that
if there is a date of 18, he will directly get 32,
friends, not at all, if you are
taking 18000 and you reserve 25000, then it totally
depends on your interview, totally
depends on your communication and your
skills, your experience letter, your
last salary, so friends, this was the
salary bracket that we were going to have, now as soon as you come and
see the qualification, then under
graduates should not apply here at all,
this vacancy is only for graduates and post graduates, there is
no role for undergraduates here at all, for undergraduates we have
other videos, you can check them there, there
we have under
Heavy vacancies for graduates, so if I
talk about it here, friends, here we have the
retirement of graduate candidates, for
retirement we need the number of candidates
100 plus, that is, we
need candidates above 100, your location is going to be
Delhi, so friends, if you are
from any other state like Noida or you are
from any other state, then for them also
I will tell you how you will apply,
but watch the video till the end, do not
skip at all and in the end I will also
tell you important tips and how
you can apply in it, friends, this
location which I told you is going to be in Delhi,
100 plus we have demand for candidates in it,
I will talk about the next point,
friends,
what is going to be the qualification experience in this, so minimum
if you have
two to three months experience in any banking profile in any product,
you have only two to three months experience
or you have six months experience
and you have proof of it, if
you show there  You can do this if you have any
experience letter or anything that
you can prove there, then you
can apply for it. Along with this, friends,
your swift is going to be full day
shift, no night shift,
banking profile, that too of ICICI
Bank. Next point comes that yes,
friends, in this your English should be good,
very good English communication
with very good Hindi communication, that means your
English and Hindi should be very good, it is
not that you are
doing it with the local language Hindi or with English, if
you are speaking Hindi then you should speak
proper Hindi, if you are speaking English then
proper, your English should be good. Along with this,
friends, if I talk, then
this job role is going to be
on roll of ICICI, that means, as you might have
seen many times that you work
for the bank, for the products of some bank,
but the ones you are on roll are of
some respected company or some third party, so it is
not like that at all here, you will be on roll
of ICICI Lombard, you can check Google.
What is this board, well
everyone knows, friend, it is such a brand name, so
friends, you have to take its approval. Now let's
talk about how to apply. First of all, let me
talk about the interview process.
Friends, there will be three rounds of interviews in this.
Your first and second round will be
conducted by telephone and for the final
round, you will have to
go to the company for face-to-face. So only those candidates should
apply who can visit, that is,
you can go for face-to-face for the final round.
If you get selected
in your first or second round, then you will have to go
face-to-face for the final round.
If you are from any corner of India or from
any other state and you also
want to apply for this profile, you are
interested in banking jobs, then friends,
what you have to do is first of all, watch this video
completely and if you feel that yes,
you are complete in this profile, you are
following this profile completely, you are
perfect in this profile, then you
can call our team. For the call, you will get it on Monday to
Saturday 10:00 AM to 25 PM. Friends, there are many
Calls come but even after that the call is
not picked up. You call after five o'clock without any reason.
You
should call as per the timing, 10:00 am to 25 pm Monday to Saturday,
not Sunday. Sunday is completely off, so do
not call us Monday to Saturday
10:00 am to 5:00 pm. You can call
them and tell them that we
want to apply for this profile
for Customer Relationship Officer, that too
in ICICI Lombard. So friends, this was today's
vacancy. Friends, we keep getting a lot of
jobs. We have vacancies from many companies.
So you
can also check our old videos. There we have a lot of
series of
vacancies which keep repeating. If you are
checking our old videos, then
that vacancy will also be either ongoing
or will be coming in some time
because our CR and Consultant is first
typed by the company, after that we
share the vacancy with you and that too through our
interviews.  We sell for Rs. Our
team supports you until you are
selected.
Friends, I will tell you clearly about our process.
When we take your interview over the
phone, if we find your
profile suitable, that you are
comfortable for this profile,
fit in this profile, then we forward your resume in that profile
and
send you for interview for that. Friends,
this is our procedure.
Now what you have to do is first of all you have to
click on the like button,
click on subscribe and hit the bell icon so
that the notifications reach you first and
go to someone else through you
and they get the job from there and it is
possible that if you share it with someone else, they
too get the job through you. Friends, for all the
support you have given us,
we receive a lot of resumes on a daily basis.
Thank you very much for that and I will meet
you again with a new video. Till then, bye bye.